[Laughter]
when you think about the first time that
we met what do you remember I remember
being on a shit-ton of mushrooms and
being 21 years old and I remember your
yellow Tyrone shirt that had that woman
on his lap screaming spank me we're
wearing and I remember you dropping down
on on your knees in front of me and
grabbing my waist and me being in total
shock it who was this guy and you just
being really cute and total magic just I
remember being so blown away by who you
were and what I saw you to be in such a
quick moment of time that it seemed that
the facts of her meeting in the words of
Brock Travis were completely
inconsequential to the amount of feeling
that I felt in the moment
and that I needed to pay attention and I
did knowing I was moving out to Atlanta
five days later after meeting you
they after the first one we're just
gonna be solving this entire time what
do you love about our relationship I
love the freedom to be me I love the
support in being me I love the deepening
that I feel every day every week every
month and every year he's constantly new
revolutions that include where we've
been and what we've seen before it's
something new and different
I love how free we are together I love
how much we make each other laugh
love it spending time with you never
gets old
every minute we get to spend together it
feels like it feels just as deeply
fulfilling even more fulfilling that did
the last time we we spent time our story
of yours gets old no hearing of anything
you have to say even if she told me
before I'm here I love how much you're
willing to embrace things that are deep
and and close to me even if it's not
something that you're passionate about
I love math II weird program things and
then you might not love that they'll
still ask me about it I'm still act
excited about it even though I can tell
you're actually excited about it just
two is way easier but you gentlemen
genuinely want to be excited about it
because you know it's important to me
there's some things I love about our
relationship
I need a box of tissue when do you feel
the closest to me
it's funny I have a hard time coming up
with the answer because I'm trying to
think of when I don't feel close to you
because it's such a it's that thing
that's so important of the vigilance
that we both exude in our relationship
to safeguard that feeling of proximity
and closeness it's this connection that
feels like it's the thing that you know
is is the rarest when did I feel closest
to you I guess it's in those moments of
pause those moments of pause I have two
answers coming up one is the one in the
moments of pause when we're not doing
because we get so wrapped up in our
routines and you know that just the day
of of whatever the day is the works
New York moving around emails phone
calls texts Facebook you know all of
that stuff and those pauses of when
everything's kind of shut off and we
have a moment just to be without without
all of the distractions
I feel closest to you and the other
times I feel closest to you ironically
is when when you're gone because it's
when you're gone that that choice of
being with you is palpable because
there's never a default to us being
together even though we've been together
for 10 years there's not a default of
our marriage meeting that were in
relationship and it's whenever you're
gone and in the absence of you know that
reminds me of this amazing choice that
we live with day to day that we
continually enact and we renew every day
with each other
of being together and so I always have
this very bittersweet gratitude for the
mystic that comes
and the wake of your absence of feeling
close to you of feeling close to that
choice of being with you and it's
tangible on those moments of the absence
i rana clay
what are you hesitant to tell me
it's challenging because I feel like
there's nothing I don't tell you you are
so supportive and understanding and we
have a bond of honesty and integrity so
if I see some girl that's really hot
like I look at her and you like that's
fine that's totally fine
so I it's challenging because I don't
feel like there's a lot that I'm
hesitant to tell you about I think maybe
those are probably the things that if I
were if I were to feel any semblance of
hesitation it would be around my
sexuality as it relates towards its
expression or feeling of anyone other
than you but I still talk like we still
talk about that so if I were to feel any
hesitation it would be probably around
that because I just feel like it's such
a it's such just an unending force
that's like this looping record it's
like no I know but again it's it's never
something that I don't tell you it's
never something that we don't talk about
it's never something isn't expressed but
if there was any hesitation I guess it
would be around that
are you worried about your body changing
after the pregnancy why or why not
I may be too detriment no you know maybe
my ass will be handed to me over the
next six months and something will just
be different and I won't be able to get
my body back like I expected to but I
guess right now I'm I'm not worried I'm
not worried because I I just I feel like
I'm in this perfect balanced state of
gratitude of what my body is capable of
like I just can't believe I'm so big and
it could grow that size and I can make a
being inside of me and support it and
feed this being and and I also feel
great about how I look right now and how
I feel and I know you're gonna kick my
ass like I know like 110 percent like
you know if I say I want to look like
this by the end of summer like you're
gonna support me in my decisions of diet
exercise and then you're gonna challenge
and drag me along with whatever it is I
felt okay so um I feel really confident
about about that and I guess like I
guess the things that I could think of
that I would be worried about is that
I'm gonna have like some stretchy vagina
for the rest of my life it's never gonna
go back to normal but if you're even
that is fine you know like you just
gotta do different set of exercises so
I'm just kind of in on the process and I
may trust that however I want my body to
be I'm totally capable of making my body
do that and I at this point I know it's
just dedication and hard work and a plan
that's it
because I thought great genetics and
it's genetics and then it's what you do
so I feel really
yeah do we have enough sex
[Music]
I've tried the word enough sex is just a
weird oxymoron one of our biggest
challenges is working in the most
magical part of either of our days into
our days I feel like just like
everything in life there are ABS inflows
that revolve around commitment stress
dedications that we have other things
that are on our plate but I guess I I
feel really satisfied at how much we
make love I feel like because of where
we are in pregnancy we've been in an ebb
and not as much of a flow I still feel
like we've we've really tried and you
know we've been really good about it
even really gonna work yeah I mean I
guess if I were to say enough sex is
feeling deeply physically connected to
your partner and that's what the
intimacy the physical intimacy allows
you to maintain and yeah I absolutely
continue to feel persistently that deep
physical connection and lusting for you
and that's really special
when do I hurt you
you only think I can think of this like
you know what are the instances that we
feel you know sharply disconnected from
each other but again that's not you
hurting me
it's triggers that bring about you know
disconnection like substance is a
trigger that drink brings about a
disconnection I'm not hurt by it but
it's very disconnecting for me and it's
painful to be in a state of
disconnection when we're you know and at
any point in our relationship and at the
same time I feel really confident the
strategies or just the templates that
we've set up to negotiate that it's you
know it's but it's still one that we
need reminders of there then I guess you
know the other thing is like but being
like a lifestyle thing that you die
before I do that's always like my
biggest fear you know and perhaps that
also rides and like on those crazy
nights of like enthusing or shit tons of
drugs or adderall or whatever it's like
you know what is this taking away from
my time with you
and then yeah that's what that's and the
other thing I can think of is my own
fear is about you know my body aging and
my aging you know but that's not again
you hurting me
that's kind of more men being there
being this very odd inverse now of all
this crazy stuff that goes on around
attraction and desire and all of that
stuff those are the things that I can
think of when I try
how do you feel about coming secondary
to the baby
and when we had our second last child
birthing class I expressed you know that
vision that I had was my nightmare was
you starting to have the baby you going
to the process of labor and screaming at
me to get out and you didn't want me
there and I guess there are two two
parts of it for me one is should there
be some kind of a physiological change
that happens from hormones and oxytocin
flooding and everything else that you
just your Center the center of your
world does in fact become this baby yeah
I'll definitely feel sad and a little
bit left out and not quite as much the
center of your world and we have been
through so much and I know that we will
get back to this maybe it's three months
maybe it's six months maybe it's a year
but we know how to climb back up this
hill and get back here and I'll do that
as many times I have to
most important person in the world
[Laughter]
we haven't needed tissues yet okay I'm
so cold I can't do cold water right now
I'm fine yeah thank you
[Laughter]
in the time we have shared together do
you have any resentments towards me no
hey the only thing I can think of is
just so much gratitude even the only
thing I can think of is it's just not
enough time
am I the best sex you've ever had yeah
one of the things that just blew me away
about you and still continues to just
blow me away about you this was
amazingly erotic and sexual you being
longer but the sexiest most profound
lover I have ever met
water it's a break here what are you
scared to tell me
I just draw such a blank I if I'm scared
of something to tell you it's kind of
like the signal that I need to tell you
something in the back of your mind are
you scared that I'll walk away no no I
think if there's one thing that over the
past ten years has really come to light
is that you and I are sitting at the
table and we're sitting at the table
we're not going anywhere but it welcomes
the table we're staying there and
whatever we have to do we're gonna do
walking away just it's nowhere in the
back of my mind the front of my mind
it's nowhere in my mind
what would make you leave me
I can't think of anything that would be
realistic of I guess if you weren't you
like if something happened where there's
like some sort of break with reality or
I don't know or something but I I just I
don't I mean I don't know I I can't
honestly think of anything I can't think
of affairs or the death of a child even
or I can't think of I can't they give
even or one of us becomes paraplegic you
know I just I can't think of anything
where that would happen
I love being with you so much it's the
most amazing part of my life
what's the biggest compromise that
you've made that I haven't acknowledged
that you haven't acknowledged biggest
compromise
right everybody this is passing is like
I don't want to answer that
this is merrily I mean honesty and being
forthright and kind of telling each
other how we feel is is a really big
part of our relationship it's why I feel
so constantly connected to you and why I
am always so excited to see you and be
with you and get to spend time with you
any chance I get and I can't think of
what have you learned about me during
this pregnancy
I'm trying to think of what I've learned
about you that's new I've been surprised
that like I've been I've been surprised
at at the fears that have come up just
that I said I may be not surprised but
that's new you know just the the Furies
of like you know how will having a baby
like displace us you know the this
nucleus like how is our Triad going to
be created that's trying to be what else
I've learned about you during this
pregnancy I feel like there's so many
things that I've depended on during this
pregnancy that just are you like you
know you know making me do my exercises
you know he needed the hell is like yeah
you know fries or something but that's
so it's also consistent with who you are
[Music]
I'm having a really hard time thinking
about what's something that I've learned
about you I feel like I'm about to learn
a lot about you as a father I feel like
it kind of feels like this has been a
little bit like this is the calm before
the storm you know like we're about to
learn a lot about each other and that
capacity but we're here to support one
another as we learn ourselves I wish I
could think of something I can't really
the thing that you're really jealous you
don't get to give birth and the crazy
totally makes heads because it's like
this peak physical experience they
you're such an extremist you could do it
you would
[Laughter]
[Music]
how do you think I'll change with this
baby
that's fine I so much of the roles that
I feel like you played for friends in
the past has had a motherly component to
it where you've helped them to see or
understand an aspect you've helped them
out in a situation you've traveled
halfway around the world to go see them
you know there's there's a very deep and
profound motherly aspect to all of the
meaningful relationships that I watch
you cultivate and so how you're going to
change I guess it doesn't feel like it's
you changing as a person so it's kind of
like I have to approach it from how is
your experience going to change in a way
that it never has been before and maybe
it's just that there won't feel like
there's a tap out you know like I I
think that might be the one thing that
seems like it's going to drastically
change is is there's you know I mean
obviously if I could like you know like
a really late night or something or
whatever and it's like dogs still need
to go out or whatever like I got your
back I got your back
always always right I mean you can't so
so it just seems like there gonna be
some aspects of this where it's like I
can't I can't I literally can't have
your back it's gotta be you and I were
so good about sharing responsibilities
whether it's dogs cleaning up house
duties whatever it is and I can't I
can't step in for a lot of this maybe we
can find out a way around it with
pumping and stuff like that but that's
you know that kind of seems like one of
the one of the biggest one of the
biggest differences is that there won't
be a tag urine kind of a thing for some
things
what do I do that detracts from our
relationship
that's another hard question for me to
answer because I don't feel like you're
doing anything that's detracting from
our relationship like I could say like
you know you're the hours that you're
putting in at work every night till 3:00
in the morning but at the same time IV
that as you're very actively trying to
add to our relationship it really like
you're so intensely focused on being
able to provide for our family that I
know that that is it's yet another thing
you're doing for us so I'm trying to
think of like what you have been so so
much in solidarity with me maybe that is
something that I can think I've been
learning about you know this pregnancy
is you really have made a statement of
being in solidarity with me during this
time of the physical changes and my own
limitations that have you know changed
and arose of being pregnant and even
like last night when I'm just done and I
just I just didn't want to go out for
the fifth night in a week even if it was
just for dinner and you stayed home with
me you know I'm trying to think of what
what you do that detracts from it and I
just feel like you're like you're so by
my side right now you've so you know
you're so by my side in in solidarity
and in a shared reality and shared
priorities and nothing sprang to mind
that that detracts and again I feel like
if there's something that arises in the
day-to-day we so quickly address that
that maybe that's why I've had
difficulty answering a lot of these like
umbrella looming questions is because we
are specifically vigilant against there
becoming an umbrella becoming a loom you
know like we've both sincerely committed
to each other to to communicate and to
breathe to press the refresh rate so
that doesn't happen because that is
dangerous that's proven to be dangerous
for us and I feel really good with where
where we are
and how are you working for us like
you're working so hard for us I just
every night you're fucking up till 3:00
or 4:00 in the morning and I feel like
I'm working - who has more power in the
relationship you or meaning that's
interesting I I guess power for me feels
of course I'm going to the definition of
power to me power feels like the ability
to influence another it's real it's
really special because I feel like one
of my biggest fears around relate long
term relationships in general is my
parents relationship where I feel like
you know my mom was the dominant figure
in the relationship my dad was
constantly succumbing and constantly
ceding his interest to make her feel
better than something that I always felt
really apprehensive about in long-term
relationships and I guess we each we
each kind of let the other know like hey
this is a big card for me this is this
is an important card for me and so you
know in situations where one of us feels
really strongly about something I feel
like we both really concede okay I see
that's a big issue for you that's that's
it's not a big deal I think you know
when we start doing with like schools of
our kid you know it's gonna get a little
bit more difficult if we if we have
contradictory viewpoints but I still
feel like we come to the table whenever
you and I are discussing something isn't
feelings based right because if it's
feelings based and it's hey this is the
way that I'm feeling and it's about
taking an opportunity to express how I
feel and feel hurt or have certain needs
met and that's that's different than a
view point a view point isn't
necessarily about feelings and it feels
like that's more where power comes in is
when I want my viewpoint to dominate or
take priority over your viewpoint I feel
like we both come to the table when we
have different viewpoints with the
understanding that I'm willing to let
this go this is just a viewpoint and
whenever we're like stuck on a viewpoint
I think we kind of bring that to each
other's attention that hey look you know
this is just a point of view this isn't
you this is just the way that you see
things and I guess I feel like that
really I I can think of so many times
where you have seated because I've felt
like that's this viewpoint or this
desire strong for me and vice versa so
it's it's really challenging to feel
like who has more power in the
relationship
it feels really balanced
what would you do if I cheated on you
[Music]
[Laughter]
well I guess I just I laugh a little bit
because it's yet another thing to you
know hey
I guess cheat in my mind is you cheat
you don't tell me you know to whatever
extent that makes sense if you come to
me and you tell me something you know
I'll tell you whatever comes up I'll
tell you if something you know if I
don't feel like a priority or I didn't
feel considered or I didn't feel I'm
disappointed you didn't talk to me about
it or hand or whatever but I guess yeah
I guess I'm having a hard time answering
because there's video cameras on I'm
fine I in a way I feel like there is no
cheat it's there's a conversation you
know and it's the courage to have a
conversation that's kind of how I feel
do you think I'm ready to be a parent
why or why not
I gonna give no one luckier on this
planet the being that gets to have you
as their mother you are so ready to be a
parent my biggest fear when you got
pregnant was here's this beautiful woman
this Austrian woman with this incredible
body and incredible everything what's
gonna happen when she gets pregnant and
that starts to change
I've heard of experiences where women
start to not like their body or take it
out on the baby and feel like this
little being is the reason that my body
has changed you embraced it you embraced
it like I feel like I've never seen a
woman embrace it then you continue to
listen to your body and and you want
this one with this amazing natural ebb
when your body started changing to the
point that you know I feel like you are
the most embracing pregnant woman I
think you said the other day I can't
imagine a woman not being able to
connect to the majesty of being pregnant
because we had heard somebody else say
it and so the question are you ready to
be a parent I mean I there's not an
aspect of it that I don't see you not
ready to embrace whether it's listening
whether it's admitting that maybe you
didn't do something quite right and
trying to do it better next time whether
it's just making sure that this child
feels so unconditionally loved and
supported there's not an aspect of
parenting that I don't feel like if you
don't already innately have inside of
your being it that you aren't ready to
just Evan flow into so yeah I think
you're ready to be a parent
what scares you the most about being a
mother
but somehow I can recreate somehow I
would be capable of recreating anything
close the dynamic that I have with my
mother and somehow you know through
whatever interaction that I could have a
child that didn't want to be close to me
when they reached adulthood when they
gained an independent mind and I'm so
ashamed about how I feel about my mom
it's so scary to think of the child that
could ever feel that way about me that
would be my biggest fear
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't have meaningful conversations this
can happen no actually it's telling if
you had a daughter what advice would you
give her regarding boys or men I would
tell her that she is the conduit of
vulnerability she has the ability it's
naturally wired in her women naturally
have this to be so deeply connected to
being vulnerable and that's something
that men so deeply need to be shown and
with that comes a great power and with
that also comes a great risk because
women who were vulnerable women who are
showing men the way can be scary and men
can do bad things and so I would ask her
and tell her to trust her intuition
about people and I would also tell her
to trust and really try to connect
people to that vulnerability of human
emotion of connection because she being
a woman is is the natural carrier she is
the conduit she is the pathway
and I could pour her with hours upon
hours of things that I would tell her
about the film and that would probably
be the one of the biggest and most
important pieces that I would tell her